https://www.dns-tvind.dk/privacy-statement/

Privacy statement
Det Nødvendige Seminarium (DNS) respects your privacy. In this Privacy Statement, we will inform you how DNS will safeguard your personal data according to current EU Laws on data protection.
Scope and acceptance
This Privacy Statement applies to how we manage personal data for all persons who enquire information about DNS.
Personal data is information that can identify you as a person, such as an e-mail address, street address or phone number. Processing your personal data is necessary for us to serve you. By providing us with your personal data, you accept the practices and terms described in this Privacy Statement. Please do not provide your personal data if you do not agree.
Storage of Personal Data
DNS uses only the company Karuny for storage of all Personal Data.Read more at: https://www.karuny.com/
Security Around our Hosting Products
For communication DNS uses https certificates for all services where personal data may be stored. For our Database services, we have added an extra layer of security where we issue personal certificates to gain access to the system. Certificates will be issued by Karuny https://www.karuny.com/ to employees of DNS on a need-to-know basis.
Why we process your personal data
To provide you with information about DNS, requires some information about you.Our aims with this are:
Provide detailed information about the program that DNS offers
Inform about and the latest developments in DNS and in some partner schools, in the form of digital newsletters.
To send you invitations to various events organized by DNS, such as cultural events, conferences and sports events.
Use of 3rd party products or services
We use some third party products or services on our website, these third party sites have separated and independent privacy policies. We, therefore, have no reparability or liability for the content and activities of the linked sites. Nonetheless, we seek to protect the integrity of our website and welcome any feedback about these sites. The sites we use are:
Zendesk for our live chat communications on the website.                                                              Facebook Pixel for monitoring and making our website more user-friendly Mailerlite for sending out information letters and newsletters.  Hotjar for monitoring and making our website more user-friendly
How we collect your personal data
We only collect information about you directly from you.We will also, with your consent, use cookies and other tracking technology when you use DNS’s website in order to optimize your experience of this. These cookies are only used to analyse website statistics.
Google Analytics: This cookie allows us to see information on our Website activities including, but not limited to page views, source and time spent on a Website. The information is depersonalized and is displayed as numbers, meaning it cannot be tracked back to individuals. This will help to protect your privacy. By using Google Analytics, we can see what content is popular on our Website, and strive to give you more of the things you enjoy reading and watching.
You can prevent the information generated by the Google cookie about your use of our Sites from being collected and processed by Google in the future by downloading and installing Google Analytics Opt-out Browser Add-on for your current web browser. This Add-on is available at http://tools.google.com/dlpage/gaoptout.
What personal data we process
The type of data that DNS process about you may be:
Your own details such as name, address, telephone number and email.
Personal data provided when filling in our application form: https://www.dns-tvind.dk/application-form/
How we store your personal data
We store your personal data on our database which is provided by Karuny.com that complies with GDPR laws on secure storing of personal data, and only people working for DNS with a valid personal certificate can access your data. We do not share your data with anyone else.
Your rights
You have the right to opt-out of receiving news and information from DNS and can do so by:
Contacting us via e-mail: info@dns-tvind.dk
Use the opt-out feature in newsletters and other mails
Access and rectification
You have the right to request a copy of your personal data. You may send us a request for this.
You also have the right to request that DNS correct any inaccuracies in your personal data. This can be done by writing an email to info@dns-tvind.dk
Data security and retention
How we keep your personal data secure
DNS takes the trust you place in us seriously. DNS is committed to prevent unauthorized access, disclosure or other deviant processing of your data. Further, DNS is committed to ensure proper use of the information and to maintain data integrity. As part of our commitment, we utilize reasonable and appropriate physical, technical, and administrative procedures and measures to safeguard the information we collect and process. DNS has implemented the following security measure:
Secure operating environments – DNS stores your data in secure operating environments that are only accessible to DNS’s employees on a need-to-know basis. DNS also follows generally accepted industry standards in this respect.
Please note that these protections do not apply to the personal data that you choose to share in public areas such as social media.
How long we store your personal data
DNS will only retain your personal data for as long as necessary for the stated purpose. This means that we may retain your personal data for a reasonable period after your last interaction with us. When the personal data that we collect is no longer required in this way, we destroy or delete it in a secure manner.
After four years since last interaction we will delete all personal data we have on you automatically. The reason for storing personal data for four years, is that our experience shows, that some people who enquire for information about the DNS programme, go through a long clarification process before making a decision to join the programme.
Changes to this Statement
If we modify our Privacy Statement, we will post the revised statement here, with an updated revision date. We encourage you to review the Statement regularly. If we make significant changes to our Statement that materially alter our privacy practices, we may also notify you by other means, such as sending an email or posting a notice on our website and/or social media pages prior to the changes taking effect.
How to contact us
We value your opinion. If you have any comments or questions about our Privacy Statement, any unresolved privacy or data use concerns that we have not addressed satisfactorily, or concerning a possible breach of your privacy, please send them to info@dns-tvind.dk . We will handle your requests or complaints confidentially. Our representative will contact you to address your concerns and outline the options regarding how these may be resolved. We aim to ensure that complaints are resolved in a timely and appropriate manner.
Privacy Statment updated:
25 June 2018
European Commission GDPR Information
